E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
E. P. Dutton & Company, Inc. Records
- Publicity files
  - Aminoff - Ambruster (Box 29)
    Aminoff, Baroness Leonie 1930-1931-1932
    Aminoff, Baroness Leonie 1928-1929
    Aminoff, Leonie - Correspondence
    Ambruster, Howard Watson
  - Amundsen - Andrews (Box 29)
    Amundsen, Roald - Correspondence
    Ancient Map of Fairy Land
    Anderson, F.I. Paul R. Reynolds 1928 - 1934
    Andersen, Homer Paul
    Andrews, Emily R.
    Andrews, General
  - Andrews I (Box 29)
    Andrews, Marietta
    Andrews, Mrs. Minnigerode
  - Andrews II (Box 29)
    Andrews, M.M. 1931-1932-1933-1934
    Andrews. Mrs. Marietta M.
  - Andrews - Angell (Box 29)
    Andrews, Marietta M. 1929
    Andrews, Marietta M. 1928
    Andrews, Mrs. W.S.
    Angell, Norman - Correspondence
  - Angell - Appel (Box 29)
    Angell, Norman - Reviews
    Angell, Sir Norman 1932-1933-1934
    Angell, Sir Norman 1930-1931
    Angell, Norman 1929
    Angell, Norman 1928
    Angell - Appel
    Angell, Norman Kennaday & Livingston
    Angoff, Charles, ed.
    Anson, Peter F.
    Anthony
    Apjohn, F.L.
    Appel, Benjamin
  - Armfield - Ashton-Wolfe (Box 30)
    Armfield, Constance Smedley
    Armstrong, William
    Armytage, Percy
    Arnold, William R.
    Artzybasheff, Boris
    Arvey, Verna
    Asch, Sholom
    Ashdown, A. Millicent
    Ashton-Wolfe, H.
  - Aspinwall - Aubry (Box 30)
    Aspinwall, Alicia Correspondence
    Asquith, Cynthia
    Atkins, Elisabeth
    Aubrey, Octar
  - Austen - Ayers (Box 30)
    Austen, Jane
    Austin, Ernest
    Aveline, Claude
    Ayala, R.P. de
    Ayer, Margaret
    Ayers, Mary B.
  - Baemeister - Bailey (Box 30)
    Baemeister, Rhoda
    Badenoch, Nena
    Baerlein, Henry
    Bailey, H.C. Correspondence
    Bailey, H.C.
  - Bailey - Barbasetti (Box 30)
    Bailey, H.C. serial rights
    Bailey, H.C. Reviews
    Baillie-Grohman, William A.
    Bainbrigge, Marion S.
    Bains, A.E.
    Baker, Laura Nelson
    Bakke, Dr. E. Wight
    Baldwin, Marguerite R.
    Baldwin, Marguerite R. 1928-1934
    Ballard, Admiral George Alexander
    Bamburg, Lillian
    Bamburg, Lillian 1928-1934
    Barbasetti, Luigi
  - Barbasetti - Barbusse (Box 30)
    Barbasetti, Luigi 1932-1933
    Barbasetti, Luigi 1930-1931
    Barbusse, Henri Bio, Photos & Items
  - Barbusse (Box 30)
    Barbusse, Henri Correspondence 1
    Barbusse, Henri Correspondence 2
  - Barbusse - Barschak (Box 30)
    Barbusse, Henri Articles and Personal Letters
    Barbusse, Henri Reviews
    Baring, Maurice Correspondence
    Barker, Elsa Correspondence
    Barker, F. Ellis
    Barker, Grainville
    Barrett, Richmond
    Barrett, Sir William F.
    Barschak, Erna
  - Barry (Box 30)
    Barry, Charles
    Barry, Charles 1934
    Barry, Charles 1929-1930
    Barry, Charles 1928
  - Bashkirtseff - Batchelder (Box 30)
    Bashkirtseff, Marie Bio and Reviews
    Bashkirtseff, Marie Correspondence
    Barker, Elsa Bio & Items - Also Correspondence
    Bruton, Paul Reviews
    Batchelder, Ann
  - Bateman - Bates (Box 30)
    Bateman, H.M.
    Bates, Katherine Lee Correspondence 1
    Bates, Katherine Lee Correspondence 2
  - Bates (Box 30)
    Bates, Ralph Reviews
    Bayley, Mary E.
    Bates, Ralph Correspondence
    Bates, Ralph Bio, Photos, Items
    Bates, Ralph Articles and Personal Letters
  - Bayne - Beck (Box 30)
    Bayne, Spencer
    Baynes, D.J.
    Baynes, Ernest Harold Correspondence & Items
    Beach, Mrs. Percy
    Beardsley, Aubrey Reviews
    Beck. Henry C.
    Beck, Henry Charelton 1934
    Beck, Hanry Charelton 1933
  - Beck - Belbenoit (Box 31)
    Beck, Henry Charlton 1930-31-32-33
    Beethoven's Letters (& Beethoven) Reviews
    Beerbohm, Max Reviews
    Beffel, Eulalie C.
    Belbenoit, Rene
  - Belbenoit (Box 31)
    Belbenoit, Rene Correspondence 1
    Belbenoit, Rene Correspondence 2
    Belbenoit, Rene Articles & Letters
    Belbenoit, Rene Biog., Photos & Items
    Belbenoit, Rene Reviews
  - Belbenoit - Bennett (Box 31)
    Belloc, Hilaire Correspondence
    Bellow, Ida Comstock
    Benet, William Rose Reviews
    Bennett, Arnols #2 Correspondence & Letter 1913-1932
  - Bennett - Bing (Box 31)
    Bennett, C.M.
    Bennett, Ernest N.
    Bennett, Richard (ILLUS.)
    Berenson, Bernhard
    Beresford, John D.
    Bernays, Edward L.
    Berry, Jean
    Best Sport Stories Releases
    Betts, C.L.
    Biber, Barbara
    Biegeleisen, J.I.
    Bing, Alexander
  - Binns - Blackwood (Box 31)
    Binns, Henry B.
    Binyon, Lawrence
    Birkeland, Joran
    Blackwell, Elizabeth
    Blackwood, Algernon
    Blackwood, Algernon Correspondence
  - Blackwood - Blakeslee (Box 31)
    Blackwood, Algernon Reader's Reports
    Blackwood, Algernon Reviews
    Blaisdell, Elinor
    Blake, William Letters
    Blake, William Reviews
    Blakeslee, Fred Gilbert 1929-1930-1931-1932-1933-1934
  - Blakeslee - Blasco-Ibanez (Box 31)
    Blakeslee, Fred Gilbert
    Blasco-Ibanez Historis la Guerra Europea de 1914-
    Blasco-Ibanez Reader's Reports
  - Blasco-Ibanez I (Box 31)
    Blasco-Ibanez Correspondence
    Blasco-Ibanez Reprint publishers
  - Blasco-Ibanez II (Box 31)
    Blasco-Ibanez #2 Biog., Photos, Items
    Blasco-Ibanez #1 Photos & Items
  - Blasco-Ibanez III (Box 31)
    Blasco-Ibanez Articles & Features - Personal Letters
    Blasco-Ibanez Articles & Personal Letters
  - Blasco-Ibanez I (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Correspondence #1
    Blasco-Ibanez Correspondence #2
    Blasco-Ibanez 1918 Correspondence
  - Blasco-Ibanez II (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez 1920 Correspondence
    Blasco-Ibanez 1921 Correspondence
    Blasco-Ibanez 1922 Correspondence
    Blasco-Ibanez Correspondence w/ Kennedy & Livingston
  - Blasco-Ibanez III (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Contract and Copyright correspondence
    Blasco-Ibanez (Untitled)
  - Blasco-Ibanez IV (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ T. Fisher Unwim and Curtis Brown
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Mrs. Margaret Gillespie
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Frances Douglas DeKalb
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ A/C/ McClura & Co.
    Blasco-Ibanez
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ George Allen & Unwin
  - Blasco-Ibanez V (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Foreign Press Service
  - Blasco-Ibanez VI (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Constable and Co.
    Blasco-Ibanez (Curtis Brown)
    Blasco-Ibanez Sr. Sunye - Spanish Chamber of Commerce
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ J.M. Dent & Sons
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w. Thomas Nelson & Sons (Edinburgh)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ miscellaneous translators
  - Blasco-Ibanez VII (Box 32)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Sempere, Llorca (Valencia)
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Duffield and Co.
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Alfred A. Knopf
    Blasco-Ibanez Corres. w/ Simpkin, Marshall
    Blasco-Ibanez Reviews
  - Blasco-Ibanez VIII (Box 32)
  - Blathwayt - Blunt (Box 32)
    Blathwayt, Raymond
    Blatt, H.K.
    Bliss, Douglas Percy
    Block, Ralph
    Bloom, Ursula
    Blucher, Evelyn
    Blum, Mrs. Albert
    Blunt, Rev. T.H. Annotated Prayer Book
  - Boccaccio - Boley (Box 32)
    Boccaccio
    Bockton, Alice M.
    Boehn, Max Von
    Boettiger, Elizabeth F.
    Bohman, Nils
    Boley, Jean
  - Bonavia - Boul (Box 32)
    Bonavia, Michale Robert
    Bond, Frederick Bligh
    Bone, David Biog, Correspondence, & Items
    Bone, David Reviews
    Bonnard, Abel
    Bonner, Mary Graham
    Bordeaux, Henri
    Bosa, Stera
    Boul, David W.
  - Boulenger - Bradley (Box 32)
    Boulenger
    Boulting, William
    Bowen, Marjorie
    Bowen, P.G.
    Bowen, Stirling
    Boy Scouts of America
    Boyd, Aubrey
    Boynton, Richard Wilson
    Brace, Timothy
    Bradley, A.G.
    Bradley William Aspenwall agent 1930-1933
    Bradley, Luther D.
    Bragg - Brine
    Bragg, William
    Bradley, Mrs.
    Bram, Dr. I
    Brazdova-Posse, Amelie
    Brebner, Percy James
    Bres, Rose Falls
    Bretherton, Vivian
    Brill, Ethel C.
    Brine, Mary D.
  - Brockway - Brooks (Box 32)
    Brockway, Sylvia Correspondence
    Brockway, Sylvia
    Brooke, Stopford
    Brookfield, A.M.
    Brooks, Elbridge S.
  - Brooks, Phillips I (Box 33)
    Brooks, Phillips Letters to Mr. Dutton, etc.
    Brooks, Phillips Carols (letters to Mr. Dutton)
    Brooks, Phillips Manuscripts
    Brooks, Phillips Unauthorized publications - NY Times ed March 1893
    Brooks, Phillips List of sermons
    Brooks, Phillips Correspondence #1
  - Brooks, Phillips II (Box 33)
    Brooks, Phillips Biog. Materials and Items
    Brooks, Phillips Thoughts from, etc
  - Brooks, Phillips III (Box 33)
    Brooks, Phillips Theological Seminaries - Mrs. Moors' Gifts to
    Brooks, Phillips Contracts and Letters
  - Brooks, Phillips IV (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Phillips V, Tribute to him at Death (Box 33)
  - Brooks, V.W. I, Reviews (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck II, Articles and Items (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck Biog., Photos and Items (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck III, Articles and Letters (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck IV, Reviews Flowering of New England (Box 33)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck V (Box 33)
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews New England Indian Summer
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews World of Wshington Irving
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews Opinions of Oliver Allston
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews Emerson & Others
  - Brooks, V.W. VI (Box 33)
    Brooks, Van Wyck Rviews Sketches In Criticism / Three Essays on America
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews Pilgramage of Henry James
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews The Ordeal of Mark Twain
    Brooks, Van Wyck Reviews On Literature Today
  - Broughton - Brown, H.C. (Box 33)
    Broughton, Averall
    Brown, Abbie Farwell
    Brown, Alice V.V.
    Brown, Ethel C. Correspondence
    Brown, Ford K.
    Brown, Henry Collins Reviews
    Brown, Henry Collins Biog. & Photos
  - Brown - Browning (Box 33)
    Brown, Louise Fargo
    Brown, Margaret Wise
    Browne, Robert T.
    Browning, Elizabeth (Letters to her sister)
  - Bruff I, The Manatee Reviews (Box 34)
  - Bruff II (Box 34)
    Bruff, Nancy #1
    Bruff, Nancy Manatee Clippings #2
  - Bruff III (Box 34)
    Bruff, Nancy Manatee Clippings #3
    Bruff, Nancy My Talon In Your Heart
    Bruff, Nancy Cider From Eden clippings & comments
  - Brundidge - Bunce (Box 34)
    Brundidge, Harry T.
    Bryson, Charles
    Bryner, Edna Correspondence
    Bucke, Dr. R.M. Correspondence
    Bucke, Dr. R.M.
    Budge, Ernest Alfred T.
    Buffman, Chem. Fd. Co.
    Bunce, William H.
  - Bullard (Box 34)
    Bullard (Reader's Reports)
    Bullard, Marion (1933-1934) deceased Dec. 18, 1950 #2
  - Bullard - Burke (Box 34)
    Bullard, Marion
    Bunyard, Edward A.
    Berdekin, Harold
    Burke, Jane Revere
    Burke, Noel
    Burman
    Burman, Ben Lucien
  - Burman - Butler (Box 34)
    Burman, Ben Lucian
    Burns, Emile
    Burrowes, Elizabeth
    Butler, A.J.
    Butler, Rohan d'O
    Butler, Don Cuthbert
    Butler, Samuel - Photos & Circulars
  - Butler I (Box 34)
    Butler, Samuel Correspondence #2 (1918-1923)
  - Butler II (Box 34)
    Butler, Samuel Correspondence #3 (1924-1934)
    Butler, Samuel Clippings - Biographical
    Butler III
    Butler, Samuel Articles & Items
    Butler, Samuel Reader's reports
    Butler, Samuel Reviews - Shrewsbury Ed. Unconscious Memory
    Butler, Samuel Reviews 1917
  - Butler IV (Box 34)
    Butler, Samuel Correspondence #1 (1909-1917)
    Butler, Samuel Reviews (Way of All Flesh)
  - Butler - Bynner (Box 34)
    Butler, Mrs. W.M. Allen
    Byrnes, J.F.
    Bynner, Witter
  - Cable - Cadby (Box 34)
    Cable, Boyd Correspondence & Letters
    Cabot, Mrs. T.H.
    Cadby, Mrs. Carine
  - Cadman - Cammaerts (Box 34)
    Cadman, Rev. S. Parkes
    Caldwell-Johnson, John
    Camehl, Mrs. George E. Correspondence on Blue China
    Cammaerts, Emile
  - Campbell (Box 35)
    Campbell, J.L.
    Campbell, J.L. Biog., Photos, Items, and Reviews
    Campbell, J.L. American Play Company
    Campbell, J.L. 1930
  - Campbell - Cannon (Box 35)
    Campbell, J.L. 1928-1929
    Campbell, Louseng Funny Feathers
    Canfiled, W.W.
    Canfield, W.W. correspondence
    Cannan, Gilbert
    Cannon, Alexander Correspondence
    Cannon, Alexander Biog., Photos, and Items
    Cannon, Alexander 1934
    Cannon, Mrs. Elizabeth Perry
  - Cannon - Carlsen (Box 35)
    Cannon, Marion
    Cannon, William
    Carly, M.
    Capes, W.P.
    Carl and Eaton
    Carleton, Patrick Letters
    Carleton, Patrick Biog, Photos, Items, Reviews
    Carlisle, Norman V.
    Carlisle, Kathleen
    Carlsen, C.L.
  - Carlson I (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy Correspondence #1
    Carlson, John Roy Photos and Clippings
    Carlson, John Roy Radio
  - Carlson (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy Lecture Coverage
    Carlson, John Roy Promotion Pieces
    Carlson, John Roy #1 Walter Wimehell's Mail
  - Carlson (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy #2 Walter Wimehell's Mail
    Carlson, John Roy #3 Walter Wimehell's Mail
  - Carlson III (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy #4 Walter Wimehell's Mail
    Carlson, John Roy The Platters
  - Carlson IV (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy Sedition Trial
    Carlson, John Roy #1 Curious Items
  - Carlson V (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy #2 Curious Items
    Carlson, John Roy Editorial List & Items
    Carlson, John Roy Photos of the Gannett's Under Cover
  - Carlson VI (Box 35)
    Carlson, John Roy Advertising #1
    Carlson, John Roy Advertising #2
    Carlson, John Roy Advertising #3
  - Carmichael - Chesterton (Box 35)
    Carmishael, W.D.
    Carotti - History of Art
    Carpenter, J.H.
    Carpenter, Jeanne Red Cross 1918 Correspondence
    Caven, Stewart
    Chain of Prayer Across the Ages
    Champion, S.G.
    Channon, Henry Biog., Photos, & Items
    Chapman-Huston, Major Desmon
    Chesser, E.S.
    Chesterton, Gilbert
  - Chevreuil - Chrisite (Box 35)
    Chrvreuil
    Child, Richard Washburn Correspondence
    Child, Richard Washburn
    Childe, Charles P.
    China Atlas and China Yearbook
    New Atlas and Commercial Gazetteer of China
    China Year Book
    Chrisman, Arthur Bowie
    Chrisman, Arthur Bowie Reviews
    Chrisman, Arthur Bowie Articles - Newbury Medal etc.
    Christian Kit
    Christie, Mrs.
  - Christy - Chute (Box 35)
    Christy, Arthur
    Christmas Book Reviews
    Christopher Quarles Reviews
    Church Book of Bunyan Meetings
    Chute, B.J.
  - Churchill - Clayden (Box 36)
    Churchill, May Thirza
    Chute, Marchette Gaylord
    Cainfarra, Camille M.
    Citrine, Walter McLennan Biog., Photos, & Items
    Citrine, Walter McLeanna Reviews
    Clark, Imogene
    Clarke, Charles Ramsay Correspondence
    Clarkson, L. (Mrs. Whitelock)
    Claxton - A Child's Grace
    Clayden, Arhur W.
  - Clemens - Clutton (Box 36)
    Clemens, W.H.
    Clements, E.H.
    Clifford, Mrs. W.K. Correspondence
    Clouston, Storer Correspondence and Items
    Clune, Frank
    Clutton-Brock, Arthur Items
    Clutton-Borck, Aurther Biog. - Photos & Items
  - Cobb - Cohen (Box 36)
    Cobb, Frank (Cobb of "The World")
    Cocke, Mrs.
    Coffin, Howard
    Cohen, Albert 1931-1932
    Cohen, Albert
    Cohen, M. (Solal)
  - Cohen (Box 36)
    Cohen, Albert 1933
    Cohen-Portheim, Paul Reviews
    Cohen-Portheim, Paul Correspondence
  - Cohen - Collins (Box 36)
    Cohen-Portheim, Paul Biog., Photos, etc.
    Calbourne, Maurice
    Colman, Elliott
    Coleman, Harry J.
    Collins, A. Frederick
    Collins, James H.
    Collins, Norman
  - Collinson - Comfort (Box 36)
    Collinson, Clifford W.
    Collinson-Morley, Mrs. L.
    Comfort, Jane Levington
    Comfort, Will Levington Biog., Photos, Items
    Comfort, Will Levington 1932
    Comfort, Will Levington 1930 1931
  - Comfort - Conrad (Box 36)
    Comfort, Will Levington Correspondence
    Cone, Helen Gray
    Cohen, Lester
    Colum. Padriac
    Connolly, Reverend Terence, S.J.
    Conrad, Jessie Correspondence
    Conrad, Jessie Biog., Photos, etc.
    Conrad, Jessie Reviews
    Consetius - Converse
    Consentius, Ernst
    Converse, Florence 1929-1930
    Converse, Florence Correspondence
  - Converse - Cook (Box 36)
    Converse, Florence 1931, 1932-33-34-35-36-37
    Converse, Florence Reviews
    Converse, Florence Biog. & Photos
    Cook, Dan
    Cook, Thomas
  - Coolidge (Box 36)
    Coolidge, Dane Correspondence
    Coolidge, Dane (untitled)
    Coolidge, Dane Articles, Special Cols. & Publicity
    Coolidge, Dane Biog., Photos, Items
    Coolidge, Dane 1928-1934
  - Coolidge - Cornillier (Box 36)
    Coolidge, Dane Reviews (old)
    Coolidge, Dane Ober
    Cappock, Charles
    Cooney, Fanny Cory Anne Louise Moore 1929-1932
    Copplestone, Bennett
    Corcos, Loris
    Cornillier
  - Corrigan - Coxe (Box 36)
    Corrigan, Douglas Biog., Photos, & Items
    Costume and Fashion Reviews
    Cothren, Marion B.
    Cowles, Edith V.
    Cox, Harding
    Coxe, George Harmon
  - Coyle I (Box 37)
    Coyle, Kathleen
    Coyle II
    Coyle, Kathleen Correspondence #2
  - Crabites - Crawford (Box 37)
    Crabite's, Pierre 1933-1934
    Craig, Gordon Biog. and Photos
    Craig, Gordon Correspondence
    Craig, Kathleen Taylor
    Cranmer-Byng, L.
    Crawford, Prof. W.J. Correspondence
    Crawford, W.J.
  - Cressy - Cross (Box 37)
    Cressy-Marcks, Violet
    Crosley, Mrs. W.S.
    Cross, Christopher
    Cross, Mrs. Helene
    Cross, Christopher Soldiers of God
  - Crowley - Crowther (Box 37)
    Crowley, Aleister
    Crownfield, Gertrude
    Crowther, J.G.
  - Cugle - Cunningham (Box 37)
    Cugle, Charles Correspondence
    Cugle, Capt. Charles H. 1933-1934
    Cugle, Capt. Charles H. 1928-1932
    Cunningham, A.B.
    Currie, Col. J.A.
    Curtin - Daru
    Curtin, Jeremiah Correspondence
    Curtiss, F. Homer
    Curtis, Paula
    Cushman, Allerton
    Cutts, A.B. Jr.
    Daglish, eric Fitch Biog.
    Daily Round - Prayerbook
    Dewey, John & Evelyn Reviews
    Daisy, Princess of Pless
    Dakers, Andrew H.
    Dale, Mrs. L.S.
    Danzinger, Dr.
    Daru, Juliska
  - Daviot - DeFiore (Box 37)
    Daviot, Gordon
    de Verona, Guido
    Davis, C.T.
    Davis, Bob (R.H.)
    Davis, Ruth Helen
    Davisson, Elizabeth Derr
    Dawson, Mrs. Scott
    Dawson-Scott, C.A.
    de Ryola, Rawon Correspondence
    de Castro, Adolphe
    de Coulevain, Pierre Correspondence
    de Coulevian, Pierre Reviews
    DeFiore, Victor
  - DeFiore - de La Mare (Box 37)
    DeFiore, Mr. V.E.
    DeKalb, Frances Douglas (See also Blasco-Ibanez I-III (Box 31) and Blasco-Ibanez I-VIII, Box 32)
    deKoven, Mrs. Reinald
    De Koven, Mrs. Ringinald Biog. & Photo
    de La Mare, Colin
  - de La Mare - Delayen (Box 37)
    de La Mare, Walter Items
    De La Posture, Mrs. Henry Correspondence
    De La Posture, Mrs. Henry Biog. and Items
    Delayen, Gaston
    Delayen, Gaston 1932-1933-1934
  - Delayen (Box 37)
    Delayen, Gaston Farrell Symons
    Delayen, Gaston 1929-30-31
    Delayen, Gaston Kennaday & Livingston
    De Prantz - DeWitt
    De Prantz, Mme (Day Monroe)
    De Rusette-Louie
    de Sola, Alis Bosy Is Faithful
    de Souza, Count Barretto Correspondence
    DeWitt, Maragaret
    DeWitt, Maragaret 1929
    DeWitt, Maragaret 1928
  - Dearmer - Dennis (Box 37)
    Dearmer, Percy, Rev.
    Deland, Margaret #1 Mr. Macrae's Correspondence w/
    Deland, Margaret #2 Correspondence
    Delehanty, Elizabeth
    Delehanty, Elizabeth Year One
    Denis, Paul
    Dennis, A.L.P. Correspondence
  - Dennis - Dixey (Box 38)
    Dennis, Mary Cable
    Dennis, Mary Cable 1933-1934
    Dent, J.M. (Memoirs) Reviews
    Dent, Richard C.
    Dexter, Walter
    Dickens Circle
    Digby, George
    Dixelius - von Astor, Mrs. Hildur
    Dixey, Marmaduke
  - Doane - Dohm (Box 38)
    Doane, W.C.
    Dodd, Lee Wilson Biog., Photos, Items
    Dodd, Lee Wilson Correspondence #1
    Dodd, Lee Wilson Correspondence #2
    Dohm, Dr. A (Jake Lingle)
  - Dole - Dunn (Box 38)
    Dole, Nathan Haskell Correspondence
    Downer, Marion
    Dragounis, Julia D.
    Dreier, K.S.
    Drew, John Correspondence
    Drew, John Biog. and Photos
    Drossner, Charles D.
    Drury, Horace B.
    Duff Gordon, Lucie (Lady)
    Dunbar, Aldis Correspondence
    Dunbar, Aldis Reviews
    Duncan, Lee
    Dunn, Violette Kimball
  - Dyson - Edwardes (Box 38)
    Dyson, Will
    Eaton, Walter Prichard
    Eckford, Euginia
    Eckford, Euginia 1930-1933
    Eddison, E.R. Correspondence
    Eddison, E.R. Biog. and Items
    Edwardes, Tickner
  - Edwards - Emery (Box 38)
    Edwards, A.H. (1920)
    Edwards, Dorothy Lee
    Einstein, Alfred
    Eldridge, Elizabeth
    Emans, Elaine V.
    Emerson, Caroline D. 1929-1933
    Emerson, Edwin
    Emery, Samuel 1928-1933
  - Emmrich - Exline (Box 38)
    Emmrich, Dorothy
    Erickson, Curtis
    Evans, Henry O.
    Everson, Florence M. 1928-1934
    Exline, Frank
  - Fairfax - Farjeon (Box 38)
    Fairfax, Beatrice (Marie Manning)
    Fairgrieve, James Items
    Fairless, Michael Correspondence and Items
    Fairless, Michael Reviews
    Fales, Dean
    Farbridge, Maurice
    Farjeon, Eleanor
  - Farnam - Ferguson (Box 38)
    Farrere, Claude Reviews
    Febrre, L.
    Feld, Rose C.
    Feldman, Harry Allen
    Ferguson, James
    Ferguson, Rachel
  - Fernau - Ferris (Box 38)
    Fernau, Merrmann (The Coming Democracy)
    Ferrero, Gina Lombroso - See Lombroso, Gina in Locke - Ludovici (Box 45)
    Ferriere, Ad.
    Ferris, Helen Biog, Photos, and Items
    Ferris, Helen Correspondence
  - Ferris - Field (Box 38)
    Ferris, Helen 1928-1933
    Ferris, Helen Reviews
    Field, Alice W.
    Field, C.C.
    Field, Hope
    Field, Rachel Correspondence
  - Field - Fishback (Box 38)
    Field, Winthrow Alice
    Fielding, William J.
    Fiery, Marion
    Findlater, Jane & Mary
    Fine, Reuben
    Finger, Charles J. Correspondence
    Finger, Charles J. 1931-1932
    Fishback, Margaret
  - Fishbein - Fleg (Box 38)
    Fishbein, Morris
    Fisher, Irving
    Fiske, Adminral Bradley A.
    Fitzgerald, Walter
    Flanders, Helen Hartness
    Flanders, Helen Hartness 1928-1930
    Fleg, Edmond Biog., Photos, and Items
    Fleg, Edmond Correspondence
    Felg, Edmond 1929-1933
  - Fleg - Foley (Box 39)
    Fleg, Edmond Reviews
    Fletcher, Peter
    Fletcher-Vane, Major Sir Francis
    Fleury, Barbara Frances
    Foldes, Lili
    Foley, James Correspondence & Items
  - Forbes - Ford (Box 39)
    Forbes, Rosita
    Ford, James Correspondence
    Ford, Julis Ellsworth
    Ford, Julia Ellsworth 1928-1931
  - Foreman - Frnakau (Box 39)
    Forman, L.L.
    Forgione, Louis Corespondence
    Forrest (Golf)
    Foss, Major Joe
    Foster, R.F. Correspondence
    Fox, Frances Margaret
    Foy, Eddie
    Franchot, Annie W. Biog.
    Franchot, Annie W. Correspondence
    Fraukau, Gilbert Reviews
  - Frankau - French (Box 39)
    Frankau, Gilbert Correspondence
    Frankau, Pamela
    Frankie In Wonderland
    Freeman, Dr. Ira M.
    Freeman, Martin Joseph 1930-1934
    French, Herbert
  - Freudlich - Funk (Box 39)
    Freundlich, Prof. Erwin Biog. & Correspondence
    Frey, Nina
    Friedman, Elisba Correspondence
    Fry, Rosalie
    Fuller, Anne
    Fuller, Raymond T.
    Funk, Wilfred
  - Gable - Gallatin (Box 39)
    Gable, J. Harris
    Gaines, Ruth
    Art and the Great Way Reviews
    Gallatin, Albert Eugene
  - Galvez - Garrett (Box 39)
    Galvez, Manuel
    Garrett, Garet
    Garrett, Garet Correspondence #2
  - Garrett (Box 39)
    Garrett, Garet 1928-1933
    Garrett, Garet (untitled)
  - Garnett - Garvan (Box 39)
    Garnett, Mrs. David
    Garnett, Edward Correspondence #2
    Garnett, Edward Correspondence #1
    Garland, Hamlin
    Garry, Georgina
    Garran 1923
  - Gauvreau - Gibbings (Box 39)
    Gauzreau, Emile
    Gay Paintings of French Int.
    Geijerstam, Af Gosta
    Georg, Eugen
    Gerard, Francis
    Gibbings, Robert
  - Gibbon - Gibbons (Box 39)
    Gibbon, John Murray
    Gibbon, John Murray 1933-1934
    Gibbon, John Murray 1930-1932
    Gibbons, The Life of (Allen Will) Reviews